{"assignment": "Paper1", "question_number": "1", "type": "standard", "question": "CRISPR was not the first genome editing technology. Which of the following were specifically cited by the paper as previously discovered genome editing methods? (mark all that apply) Mark all that apply", "choices": ["Type II Restriction Endonucleases", "Zinc Fingers (ZFs)", "transcription activator-like effectors (TALEs)", "SURVEYOR", "Homing Meganucleases"], "correct_answers": ["Zinc Fingers (ZFs)", "transcription activator-like effectors (TALEs)", "Homing Meganucleases"]}
{"assignment": "Paper1", "question_number": "2", "type": "standard", "question": "What is the role of the CRISPR/Cas9 system in nature?", "choices": ["It is an adaptive immune system in bacteria", "It is part of the viral infection machinery", "It is an adaptive immune system in eukaryotes", "It is part of the transposon machinery", "It is part of the prokaryotic RNA-processing machinery"], "correct_answers": ["It is an adaptive immune system in bacteria"]}
{"assignment": "Paper1", "question_number": "3", "type": "standard", "question": "In Figure 1A, the researchers tested the effectiveness of Nuclear Localization Sequences (NLS) inserted at various places along SpCas9 and SpRNaseIII. Why was the experiment necessary? What did their results show for Cas9? (Use the format They saw X, indicating Y.) What did their results show for RNaseIII? (same format)", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Paper1", "question_number": "4", "type": "standard", "question": "Which panel showed that SpRNaseIII was not necessary?", "choices": ["Figure 1A", "Figure 1B", "Figure 1C", "Figure 1D", "Figure 1E"], "correct_answers": ["Figure 1D"]}
{"assignment": "Paper1", "question_number": "5", "type": "standard", "question": "Which type of mutation is most common when using CRISPR to edit the EMX locus (Figure 1E)?", "choices": ["Base Changes", "Insertions", "Deletions", "Having multiple types simultaneously"], "correct_answers": ["Deletions"]}
{"assignment": "Paper1", "question_number": "6-10", "type": "matching", "options": ["Control", "Chimeric RNA", "crRNA", "EMX1 Protospacer Target (1, 2, 3, 4, 5)", "Bands in each lane"], "matches": [{"prompt": "Independent variable with multiple levels (first independent variable)", "answer": "(D)"}, {"prompt": "The negative control for the first independent variable", "answer": "(A)"}, {"prompt": "Independent variable with a single level (second independent variable). \u200b\u200b\u200b\u200b\u200b\u200b\u200bHint: the negative control for this variable is not considered a level of treatment.", "answer": "(B)"}, {"prompt": "The negative control for the second independent variable", "answer": "(C)"}, {"prompt": "Dependent variable", "answer": "(E)"}]}
{"assignment": "Paper1", "question_number": "6", "type": "standard", "question": "Independent variable with multiple levels (first independent variable)", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Paper1", "question_number": "7", "type": "standard", "question": "The negative control for the first independent variable", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Paper1", "question_number": "8", "type": "standard", "question": "Independent variable with a single level (second independent variable). \u200b\u200b\u200b\u200b\u200b\u200b\u200bHint: the negative control for this variable is not considered a level of treatment.", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Paper1", "question_number": "9", "type": "standard", "question": "The negative control for the second independent variable", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Paper1", "question_number": "0", "type": "standard", "question": "Dependent variable", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Paper1", "question_number": "1", "type": "standard", "question": "What type of control is labeled \"control\" in Figure 2C?", "choices": ["Negative Control for making the chimera", "Positive Control showing efficient cutting", "Validation (Loading) Control showing the lanes are all evenly loaded", "Negative Control for adding a spacer"], "correct_answers": ["Negative Control for adding a spacer"]}
{"assignment": "Paper1", "question_number": "2", "type": "standard", "question": "What is the hypothesis of Figure 3A and B?", "choices": ["Chimeric RNAs are more efficient than crRNA:tracrRNA duplexes", "Cas9 only cuts where the protospacer matches perfectly (it is highly specific)", "CRISPR is more efficient than TALEN", "CRISPR can be used to stimulate homologous recombination"], "correct_answers": ["Cas9 only cuts where the protospacer matches perfectly (it is highly specific)"]}
{"assignment": "Paper1", "question_number": "3", "type": "standard", "question": "Based on the data in Figure 3D, rank the efficiency of TALENS, CRISPR with chimeric RNA, and CRISPR with crRNA from most effective to least effective.", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Paper1", "question_number": "4", "type": "standard", "question": "Which of the following is/are a valid conclusion based on Figure 4A-E? (mark all that apply) Mark all that apply", "choices": ["The nickase version stimulates HR but not NHEJ", "The WT version stimulates NHEJ but not HR", "The nickase version stimulates both HR and NHEJ", "The WT version stimulates both NHEJ and HR"], "correct_answers": ["The nickase version stimulates HR but not NHEJ", "The WT version stimulates both NHEJ and HR"]}
{"assignment": "Paper1", "question_number": "5", "type": "standard", "question": "What type of control is shown in the figure? (labeled \"control\" throughout)", "choices": ["Positive control for pigmentation", "Positive control for neuronal defects", "Negative control for CRISPR", "Validation control showing the embryo injections successfully delivered the Cas9"], "correct_answers": ["Negative control for CRISPR"]}
{"assignment": "Paper1", "question_number": "6", "type": "standard", "question": "Which of the following is a valid conclusion based on the data in this figure?", "choices": ["All of the protospacers had the same efficiency", "The spacer targeting golden was the least efficient", "The eGFP protospacer did not work when combined with the others", "Combining the protospacers affected their efficiency compared to injecting each individually"], "correct_answers": ["The spacer targeting golden was the least efficient"]}
{"assignment": "Paper1", "question_number": "7", "type": "standard", "question": "Why were six penta-KO animals analyzed?", "choices": ["To find the average effectiveness of multiplexed targeting", "To show that injections did not vary day to day", "Because mistakes were made for some of the replicates", "They each received a different treatment", "Some were controls"], "correct_answers": ["To find the average effectiveness of multiplexed targeting"]}
{"assignment": "Paper1", "question_number": "8", "type": "standard", "question": "What type of control is shown in E'?", "choices": ["Negative control for GFP mutagenesis", "Positive control for knockout of GFP", "Validation control showing the GFP gene was present even though not always observed in the embryos due to nonmosaic disruption", "Loading control showing GFP was evenly distributed in the embryos"], "correct_answers": ["Validation control showing the GFP gene was present even though not always observed in the embryos due to nonmosaic disruption"]}
{"assignment": "Paper1", "question_number": "9", "type": "standard", "question": "The paper shows that fusing the crRNA to the tracrRNA (chimeric RNA) is weaker than when separate, but they never explain why. Create a hypothesis to explain the weaker cutting and design an experiment to test it. Include the following: Hypothesis (1 pt): Experimental Design and Controls (2 pts): Results if correct (1 pt): Results if incorrect (1 pt):", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Paper2", "question_number": "1", "type": "standard", "question": "WASP was already known to bind what components before they started their study? (mark all that apply) Mark all that apply", "choices": ["Signaling pathway proteins (Nck, Fyn, Fgr, etc.)", "Cdc42", "Rac (weakly)", "Rho", "proline-rich domains"], "correct_answers": ["Signaling pathway proteins (Nck, Fyn, Fgr, etc.)", "Cdc42", "Rac (weakly)"]}
{"assignment": "Paper2", "question_number": "2", "type": "standard", "question": "WIP stands for WASP Interacting Protein, which is not a very informative name. What method was used to identify WIP initially?", "choices": ["Co-immuno Precipitation", "Bioinformatic Analysis", "Yeast-two hybrid screen", "Fluorescent confocal microscopy", "Northern Blots"], "correct_answers": ["Yeast-two hybrid screen"]}
{"assignment": "Paper2", "question_number": "3", "type": "standard", "question": "What is the role of GST and MBP in Figure 2? (mark all that apply) Mark all that apply", "choices": ["One or both are epitope tags in the Western Blot", "They are Affinity tags in the CoIP", "They are enzymes that catalyze the formation of a dye", "They are activators that help the two proteins being tested to bind."], "correct_answers": ["One or both are epitope tags in the Western Blot", "They are Affinity tags in the CoIP"]}
{"assignment": "Paper2", "question_number": "4-6", "type": "matching", "options": ["Positive Control", "Negative Control", "Experimental Sample", "Independent Variable", "Dependent Variable", "Validation Control"], "matches": [{"prompt": "GST", "answer": "(B)"}, {"prompt": "Lysate", "answer": "(F)"}, {"prompt": "GST-WIP", "answer": "(C)"}]}
{"assignment": "Paper2", "question_number": "4", "type": "standard", "question": "GST", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Paper2", "question_number": "5", "type": "standard", "question": "Lysate", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Paper2", "question_number": "6", "type": "standard", "question": "GST-WIP", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Paper2", "question_number": "7", "type": "standard", "question": "What is the role of the wildtype (full length) WASP and WIP in Figure 3?", "choices": ["Negative Controls", "Positive Controls", "Treatment Groups", "Validation Controls"], "correct_answers": ["Negative Controls"]}
{"assignment": "Paper2", "question_number": "8", "type": "standard", "question": "What was the smallest deletion construct of WASP that bound WIP (of the ones shown below)?", "choices": ["WASP (WT)", "WASP 1-270", "WASP 1-170", "WASP 1-137", "WASP 139-270"], "correct_answers": ["WASP 1-170"]}
{"assignment": "Paper2", "question_number": "9", "type": "standard", "question": "What is the smallest WIP deletion construct that bound WASP?", "choices": ["WIP 4 (WT)", "WIP 321-416", "WIP 321-376", "WIP 377-503"], "correct_answers": ["WIP 377-503"]}
{"assignment": "Paper2", "question_number": "0", "type": "standard", "question": "In Figure 4, what cell types expressed WIP at the highest level?", "choices": ["Heart", "Placenta", "Kidney", "PBMC"], "correct_answers": ["PBMC"]}
{"assignment": "Paper2", "question_number": "1", "type": "standard", "question": "What is the purpose of bands at the bottom of Figure 4?", "choices": ["A loading control--a type of validation that checks for even loading in the gel.", "A positive control showing that the WIP probe works.", "An input control--a type of validation that checks to see if a protein/RNA/etc. is present in the original sample.", "A negative control for WIP expression"], "correct_answers": ["A loading control--a type of validation that checks for even loading in the gel."]}
{"assignment": "Paper2", "question_number": "2", "type": "standard", "question": "In Figure 5, what is pcDNA3?", "choices": ["The type of cells being used.", "The plasmid backbone used to clone different versions of WIP.", "The name of a drug used to stimulate WIP expression.", "An antibody recognizing WIP."], "correct_answers": ["The plasmid backbone used to clone different versions of WIP."]}
{"assignment": "Paper2", "question_number": "3", "type": "standard", "question": "Figure 5B uses TRITC-labelled Phalloidin stain. TRITC is a fluorescent marker. What does Phalloidin bind? Which panel(s) show(s) a negative control? (justify your answer) Which panel showed increased actin polymerization? (justify your answer)", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Paper2", "question_number": "4", "type": "standard", "question": "What is the conclusion of Figure 6?", "choices": ["WIP binds to BJAB", "WIP binds to GST in B cells", "WIP binds profilin", "WIP polymerizes actin"], "correct_answers": ["WIP binds profilin"]}
{"assignment": "Paper2", "question_number": "5", "type": "standard", "question": "The paper suggests that WIP binds to SH3 domain-containing proteins because it contains a particular proline-rich domain (Figure 1D). Design an experiment to test that WIP does bind an SH3 domain. Include the following: Hypothesis (1 pt): Experimental Design and Controls (2 pts): Results if correct (1 pt): Results if incorrect (1 pt):", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Paper2", "question_number": "6", "type": "standard", "question": "What is the general effect of adding profilin to actin in vitro?", "choices": ["It increases net polymerization", "It decreases net polymerization", "It has no effect on net polymerization"], "correct_answers": ["It increases net polymerization"]}
{"assignment": "Paper2", "question_number": "7", "type": "standard", "question": "What is the general effect of adding thymosin to actin in vitro?", "choices": ["It increases net polymerization", "It decreases net polymerization", "It has no effect on net polymerization"], "correct_answers": ["It decreases net polymerization"]}
{"assignment": "Paper2", "question_number": "8", "type": "standard", "question": "What is the effect on the initial rate of actin polymerization when adding less than 2 uM profilin?", "choices": ["It increases the initial rate", "It decreases the initial rate", "It has no effect on the initial rate"], "correct_answers": ["It has no effect on the initial rate"]}
{"assignment": "Paper2", "question_number": "9", "type": "standard", "question": "What is the dependent variable in the first figure (Figure 4)?", "choices": ["Time", "Light Scattering (cps)", "G-actin concentration at the beginning of the experiment", "Profilin concentration", "Presence of a drug"], "correct_answers": ["Light Scattering (cps)"]}
{"assignment": "Paper3", "question_number": "1", "type": "standard", "question": "What was already known when the paper was published? (Mark all that apply) Mark all that apply", "choices": ["Transcriptional co-activators had been identified", "Some co-activators acetylate histones", "At least four HAT complexes had been identified", "Histone Deacetylases can be linked to repressors"], "correct_answers": ["Transcriptional co-activators had been identified", "Some co-activators acetylate histones", "At least four HAT complexes had been identified", "Histone Deacetylases can be linked to repressors"]}
{"assignment": "Paper3", "question_number": "2", "type": "standard", "question": "What is VP16?", "choices": ["A transcriptional repressor protein in yeast", "A transcriptional activator protein in yeast", "A transcriptional activator domain from a virus", "A transcriptional repressor domain from a virus", "A transcription co-activator with known histone acetyltransferase activity"], "correct_answers": ["A transcriptional activator domain from a virus"]}
{"assignment": "Paper3", "question_number": "3", "type": "standard", "question": "In Figure 1A, the researchers tested the hypothesis that VP16 bound to HAT complexes by conducting a Co-immunoprecipitation (CoIP) experiment. Identify the following key features of their experimental design What is the role of GST in the GST-VP16 and GST-Gcn4 constructs? What is the negative control? What validation control did they use? Which HAT complexes were bound by VP16? Which HAT complexes were bound by Gcn4? Which HAT complex does not acetylate H3?", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Paper3", "question_number": "4", "type": "standard", "question": "Truncating VP16 at amino acid 456 has what effect on HAT binding?", "choices": ["Completely blocks binding", "Partially blocks binding", "Enhances binding", "Has no effect on binding"], "correct_answers": ["Partially blocks binding"]}
{"assignment": "Paper3", "question_number": "5", "type": "standard", "question": "Which of the following is/are negative controls in Figure 2? Mark all that apply", "choices": ["control", "GST", "GST-VP16 (the WT version)", "Supernatant"], "correct_answers": ["GST", "GST-VP16 (the WT version)"]}
{"assignment": "Paper3", "question_number": "6", "type": "standard", "question": "Which of the following is a valid conclusion from Figure 2?", "choices": ["SAGA binds VP16 upstream of where NuA4 binds", "SAGA binds VP16 downstream of where NuA4 binds", "SAGA and VP16 both bind in the upstream and downstream portions of VP16", "SAGA and NuA4 both bind VP16 at the same location"], "correct_answers": ["SAGA and NuA4 both bind VP16 at the same location"]}
{"assignment": "Paper3", "question_number": "7", "type": "standard", "question": "Tritium (3H) labelling in Figure 3 specifically marks...", "choices": ["All histones", "H3 histones", "Acetylated histones", "Phosphorylated histones"], "correct_answers": ["Acetylated histones"]}
{"assignment": "Paper3", "question_number": "8", "type": "standard", "question": "In Figure 3, what type of gel is used?", "choices": ["Native Gel", "Denaturing (SDS) gel", "Denaturing (SDS) and Reducing (Beta-mercaptoethanol) gel", "Agarose gel"], "correct_answers": ["Native Gel"]}
{"assignment": "Paper3", "question_number": "9", "type": "standard", "question": "Figures 3 and 4 show Gel Shift Assays. What determines how high the shifted band is?", "choices": ["The size of the DNA", "The type of radioactive label used", "The size of the protein binding the nucleosomes", "The extent of radioactive isotope labeling"], "correct_answers": ["The size of the protein binding the nucleosomes"]}
{"assignment": "Paper3", "question_number": "0", "type": "standard", "question": "In Figures 3 and 4, what two factors determine the brightness or intensity of the band? Mark all that apply", "choices": ["The number of radioactive acetyl groups added to the histones", "The size of the HAT binding the DNA", "The strength of the protein binding", "The amount of time the gel was run"], "correct_answers": ["The number of radioactive acetyl groups added to the histones", "The strength of the protein binding"]}
{"assignment": "Paper3", "question_number": "1", "type": "standard", "question": "Which of the following are experimental design differences between Figure 3 and Figure 4? Mark all that apply", "choices": ["Some HATs were not tested both times.", "The HAT complex was heat-inactivated in only one figure.", "The number of doses of VP16 was not consistent.", "The radioactive labels were used to mark different things in each experiment.", "Different types of gels were used in each figure."], "correct_answers": ["Some HATs were not tested both times.", "The HAT complex was heat-inactivated in only one figure.", "The number of doses of VP16 was not consistent."]}
{"assignment": "Paper3", "question_number": "12-14", "type": "matching", "options": ["Panel 5A", "Panel 5B", "Panel 5C", "Panel 5D"], "matches": [{"prompt": "VP16 mediated transcriptional activation is enhanced by HATs", "answer": "(B) Panel 5B"}, {"prompt": "The HAT complex activates transcription by acetylating histones", "answer": "(D) Panel 5D"}, {"prompt": "HATs act by interacting with the histones, not RNA Polymerase", "answer": "(C) Panel 5C"}]}
{"assignment": "Paper3", "question_number": "2", "type": "standard", "question": "VP16 mediated transcriptional activation is enhanced by HATs", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Paper3", "question_number": "3", "type": "standard", "question": "The HAT complex activates transcription by acetylating histones", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Paper3", "question_number": "4", "type": "standard", "question": "HATs act by interacting with the histones, not RNA Polymerase", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Paper3", "question_number": "5", "type": "standard", "question": "The paper shows that activators bind HATs to direct acetylation. However, they never show that activator binding is necessary for the HAT to bind the histones. Design an experiment to show that HATs do not bind histones unless the activator is present. Include the following: Hypothesis (1 pt): Experimental Design and Controls (2 pts): Results if correct (1 pt): Results if incorrect (1 pt):", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Paper3", "question_number": "6", "type": "standard", "question": "What are \"Flag\" and \"HA\"?", "choices": ["Affinity tags - additions to a protein to help it bind something other than an antibody", "Epitope tags - additions to a protein to create an antibody binding site", "Special radioactive tags", "Proteins expressed at constant levels across all samples"], "correct_answers": ["Epitope tags - additions to a protein to create an antibody binding site"]}
{"assignment": "Paper3", "question_number": "7", "type": "standard", "question": "According to panel A, which HDAC(s) bind(s) TLX? Mark all that apply", "choices": ["HDAC1", "HDAC2", "HDAC3", "HDAC5", "HDAC7"], "correct_answers": ["HDAC3", "HDAC5", "HDAC7"]}
{"assignment": "Paper3", "question_number": "8", "type": "standard", "question": "Is TLX mRNA more highly expressed in proliferating or differentiated neurons?", "choices": ["Proliferating", "Differentiated", "Both equally", "It depends on the HDAC", "There was no loading control, so we cannot tell from the data"], "correct_answers": ["Proliferating"]}
{"assignment": "Paper3", "question_number": "9", "type": "standard", "question": "Which of the following is a valid conclusion for the fluorescence microscopy data?", "choices": ["TLX and HDACs are expressed in different cells", "TLX and HDACs are in the same cells, but are enriched in different organelles", "TLX binds HDACs", "TLX and HDACs are co-localized in the same cells"], "correct_answers": ["TLX and HDACs are co-localized in the same cells"]}
{"assignment": "Paper4", "question_number": "1", "type": "standard", "question": "Which of the following is a major gap in knowledge highlighted in the introduction?", "choices": ["Whether APC is an E3 ligase", "The order of E1, E2 and E3 proteins", "Degradation targets of APC", "The identity of the E2s it works with"], "correct_answers": ["The identity of the E2s it works with"]}
{"assignment": "Paper4", "question_number": "2", "type": "standard", "question": "Which E2 proteins were shown to interact with APC in Figure 1? (Mark all that apply) Mark all that apply", "choices": ["Ubc1", "Ubc2", "Ubc3", "Ubc4", "Ubc8", "Ubc9", "Ubc13"], "correct_answers": ["Ubc1", "Ubc4"]}
{"assignment": "Paper4", "question_number": "3", "type": "standard", "question": "Figure 1 shows 35S labeled securin. What is the role of this protein?", "choices": ["E1", "E2", "E3", "E4", "Target (protein marked for degradation)"], "correct_answers": ["Target (protein marked for degradation)"]}
{"assignment": "Paper4", "question_number": "4", "type": "standard", "question": "According to Figure 2B, what type of ubiquitination does Ubc1 mainly catalyze?", "choices": ["Monoubiquitination", "Multiubiquitination", "Polyubiquitination (K29 chains)", "Polyubiquitination (K48 chains)", "Polyubiquitination (K63 chains)"], "correct_answers": ["Polyubiquitination (K48 chains)"]}
{"assignment": "Paper4", "question_number": "5", "type": "standard", "question": "According to Figure 2B, what type of ubiquitination does Ubc4 mainly catalyze?", "choices": ["Monoubiquitination", "Multiubiquitination", "Polyubiquitination (K29 chains)", "Polyubiquitination (K48 chains)", "Polyubiquitination (K63 chains)"], "correct_answers": ["Multiubiquitination"]}
{"assignment": "Paper4", "question_number": "6", "type": "standard", "question": "How many ubiquitins does Ubc4 add to cyclin?", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Paper4", "question_number": "7", "type": "standard", "question": "Which feature of the gel in Figure 3A can be used to calculate cyclin turnover (number of proteins with at least one ubiquitin)?", "choices": ["Band Intensity", "Number of Bands", "Height of Bands", "Amount of Ubc Protein added", "None of the above"], "correct_answers": ["Band Intensity"]}
{"assignment": "Paper4", "question_number": "8", "type": "standard", "question": "Which feature of the gel in Figure 3A can be used to calculate cyclin processivity (the number of ubiquitins per molecule)?", "choices": ["Band Intensity", "Number of Bands", "Height of Bands", "Amount of Ubc Protein added", "None of the above"], "correct_answers": ["Number of Bands"]}
{"assignment": "Paper4", "question_number": "9", "type": "standard", "question": "Figure 4A and B test the hypothesis that Ubc1 and 4 are more efficient when the target protein already has at least one ubiquitin attached. What are the two independent variables? What is/are the negative control(s)? (Justify your answer) For each E2, was the hypothesis confirmed or rejected? How do you know?", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Paper4", "question_number": "0", "type": "standard", "question": "What do the results of Figure 5 show about the role of the UBA domain? (Mark all that apply) Mark all that apply", "choices": ["It increases processivity", "It decreases processivity", "It increases turnover", "It decreases turnover"], "correct_answers": ["It increases processivity", "It decreases turnover"]}
{"assignment": "Paper4", "question_number": "1", "type": "standard", "question": "Which of the following genetic lines showed delayed or arrested cell division in Figure 7? Mark all that apply", "choices": ["Wild Type", "PGAL1UBC1", "ubc4-delta", "PGAL1UBC1 ubc4-delta"], "correct_answers": ["PGAL1UBC1", "ubc4-delta", "PGAL1UBC1 ubc4-delta"]}
{"assignment": "Paper4", "question_number": "12-14", "type": "matching", "options": ["Figure 1", "Figure 2", "Figure 3", "Figure 4", "Figure 5", "Figure 6", "Figure 7"], "matches": [{"prompt": "Human E2-25K works like Ubc1", "answer": "(F) Figure 6"}, {"prompt": "Ubc1 + Ubc4 is more efficient than either alone", "answer": "(D) Figure 4"}, {"prompt": "Ubc1 and Ubc4 both interact with APC", "answer": "(A) Figure 1"}]}
{"assignment": "Paper4", "question_number": "2", "type": "standard", "question": "Human E2-25K works like Ubc1", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Paper4", "question_number": "3", "type": "standard", "question": "Ubc1 + Ubc4 is more efficient than either alone", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Paper4", "question_number": "4", "type": "standard", "question": "Ubc1 and Ubc4 both interact with APC", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Paper4", "question_number": "5", "type": "standard", "question": "The paper shows that the UBA domain is important for processivity (adding multiple ubiquitin in a chain). One hypothesis is that it binds the ubiquitin already attached to the target protein to help hold the E2 in place. Design an experiment to test this. Hypothesis (1 pt): Experimental design/controls (2 pts): Results if correct (1 pt): Results if incorrect (1 pt):", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Paper4", "question_number": "6", "type": "standard", "question": "\"Cbl-c WT\" is what type of sample?", "choices": ["Negative Control", "Positive Control", "Validation Control", "Experimental Sample"], "correct_answers": ["Negative Control"]}
{"assignment": "Paper4", "question_number": "7", "type": "standard", "question": "Which of the following is an independent variable in panel A? Mark all that apply", "choices": ["Mutation of Cbl-c", "Addition of E2", "Addition of Src", "Band Brightness", "Band size (height on the gel)"], "correct_answers": ["Mutation of Cbl-c", "Addition of E2", "Addition of Src"]}
{"assignment": "Paper4", "question_number": "8", "type": "standard", "question": "What is the role of the gel \"IB: Cbl-c\" in panel B?", "choices": ["Negative Control", "Positive Control", "Validation Control", "Experimental Sample", "There was no loading control, so we cannot tell from the data"], "correct_answers": ["Validation Control"]}
{"assignment": "Paper4", "question_number": "9", "type": "standard", "question": "Which of the following is a valid conclusion for the figure when both panels are considered together? (pTyr recognizes any phosphorylated tyrosine, no matter where in the protein)", "choices": ["Cbl-c does not get phosphorylated at position 341", "Cbl-c is phosphorylated only at position 341, and this leads to ubiquitination", "Cbl-c gets phosphorylated at several positions, but position 341 is the one necessary for ubiquitination", "Cbl-c gets phosphorylated as several positions, including position 341, but another position is the one necessary for ubiquitination"], "correct_answers": ["Cbl-c gets phosphorylated at several positions, but position 341 is the one necessary for ubiquitination"]}
{"assignment": "Paper5", "question_number": "1", "type": "standard", "question": "According to the paper, what was already known about Rab1 at the time of publication? (Mark all that apply) Mark all that apply", "choices": ["It had a role in ER to Golgi transport", "It is a GTPase", "It governed flow of proteins between intracellular compartments", "It binds beta-COP", "It is activated by SAR1 GAP"], "correct_answers": ["It had a role in ER to Golgi transport", "It is a GTPase", "It governed flow of proteins between intracellular compartments"]}
{"assignment": "Paper5", "question_number": "2", "type": "standard", "question": "The paper shows that Rab1 binds to beta-COP, but it never shows if this binding is GTP dependent. Design an experiment to show that Rab1 binds beta-COP only when in the GTP-bound state. Include the following: Hypothesis (1 pt): Experimental Design and Controls (2 pts): Results if correct (1 pt): Results if incorrect (1 pt):", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Paper5", "question_number": "3", "type": "standard", "question": "Based on this data, where are PLN and COPI located?", "choices": ["In the cytoplasm", "In the nucleus", "In the Golgi", "In the ER", "Throughout the entire cell"], "correct_answers": ["In the cytoplasm"]}
{"assignment": "Paper5", "question_number": "4", "type": "standard", "question": "Which of the following is a valid conclusion from panel A?", "choices": ["PLN binds SERCA", "PLN is co-localized with SERCA", "PLN binds COPI", "PLN is co-localized with COPI"], "correct_answers": ["PLN is co-localized with COPI"]}
{"assignment": "Paper5", "question_number": "5", "type": "standard", "question": "What is the role of 1D11?", "choices": ["Affinity Tag", "Epitope Tag", "Antibody", "Bead", "Mutation"], "correct_answers": ["Antibody"]}
{"assignment": "Paper5", "question_number": "6", "type": "standard", "question": "According to the data in this figure, PLN binds to which proteins? Mark all that apply", "choices": ["SERCA2", "COPI", "ARFGAP", "ARF", "IGG"], "correct_answers": ["SERCA2", "COPI", "ARFGAP", "ARF"]}
{"assignment": "Paper6", "question_number": "1", "type": "standard", "question": "An \"agonist\" is a drug that mimics a ligand to activate a receptor. What agonist is used to stimulate the beta2-adrenergic receptor in this paper?", "choices": ["Isoprenaline", "Adrenaline", "Leu", "CQ", "NH4Cl"], "correct_answers": ["Isoprenaline"]}
{"assignment": "Paper6", "question_number": "2", "type": "standard", "question": "In Figure 1, the researchers tested recycling of several Beta2-AR mutants. Describe this factorial experiment. What are the two independent variables? (1 pt) What is the negative control for each? (1 pt) What is the baseline used to normalize the data in panel B? (1/2 pt) What label was used to measure the amount of receptor present? (1/2 pt)", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Paper6", "question_number": "3", "type": "standard", "question": "Which of the following is a valid conclusion for Figure 2A?", "choices": ["Mutating the Beta2-AR tail leads to increased expression of the receptor in the cytoplasm", "Mutating the Beta2-AR tail blocks lysosome function, causing the protein to build up in endocytic vesicles", "Mutating the Beta2-AR tail blocks formation of the multi-vesicular body, so the protein does not get degraded", "Mutating the Beta2-AR tail blocks its recycling to the surface"], "correct_answers": ["Mutating the Beta2-AR tail blocks its recycling to the surface"]}
{"assignment": "Paper6", "question_number": "4", "type": "standard", "question": "Why is the Beta2-AR curve lower than the Beta2-AR-Ala curve in Figure 2B?", "choices": ["Beta2-AR-Ala is recycled more efficiently, so more signal is detected", "Beta2-AR is recycled more efficiently, so it is less resistant to surface treatments that remove the label", "Beta2-AR-Ala is not degraded by the lysosome efficiently, so more signal is detected", "Beta2-AR-Ala is not endocytosed efficiently, so more signal is detected"], "correct_answers": ["Beta2-AR is recycled more efficiently, so it is less resistant to surface treatments that remove the label"]}
{"assignment": "Paper6", "question_number": "5", "type": "standard", "question": "Which of the following are used to block lysosome function in Figure 2C? Mark all that apply", "choices": ["CTL", "Leu", "CQ", "NH4CL", "Iso"], "correct_answers": ["Leu", "CQ", "NH4CL"]}
{"assignment": "Paper6", "question_number": "6", "type": "standard", "question": "Why did they use the transferrin receptor (which is an example of the constitutive pathway of endocytosis)?", "choices": ["Constitutive pathway receptors are always recycled", "Constitutive pathway receptors are always degraded in the lysosome", "Constitutive pathway receptors do not need ligand to be endocytosed", "Transferrin receptors are also recycled by binding EBP50"], "correct_answers": ["Constitutive pathway receptors are always recycled"]}
{"assignment": "Paper6", "question_number": "7", "type": "standard", "question": "Figure 4 shows that phosphorylation of the receptor at a particular amino acid prevents recycling. Which kinase affects Beta2-AR recycling? How do you know? Which amino acid is phosphorylated? How was its effect tested? What effect does that phosphorylation have on EBP50 binding? How do you know?", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Paper6", "question_number": "8", "type": "standard", "question": "In Figure 3C, what happened when they overexpressed WT EBP50?", "choices": ["Degradation increased", "Degradation Decreased", "Degradation stayed the same"], "correct_answers": ["Degradation increased"]}
{"assignment": "Paper6", "question_number": "9-11", "type": "matching", "options": ["Panel 1A", "Panel 1B", "Panel 2A", "Panel 2B", "Panel 2C", "Panel 3A", "Panel 3B", "Panel 3C", "Panel 3D", "Panel 4A", "Panel 4B", "Panel 4C", "Panel 4D"], "matches": [{"prompt": "The cytoplasmic tail of Beta2-AR is essential for recycling", "answer": "(A) Panel 1A"}, {"prompt": "Beta2-AR binds EBP50", "answer": "(F) Panel 3A"}, {"prompt": "Beta2-AR is specifically degraded by the lysosome", "answer": "(E) Panel 2C"}]}
{"assignment": "Paper6", "question_number": "9", "type": "standard", "question": "The cytoplasmic tail of Beta2-AR is essential for recycling", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Paper6", "question_number": "0", "type": "standard", "question": "Beta2-AR binds EBP50", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Paper6", "question_number": "1", "type": "standard", "question": "Beta2-AR is specifically degraded by the lysosome", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Paper6", "question_number": "2", "type": "standard", "question": "The paper shows that actin is essential for recycling, but never actually shows that the receptors bound to them to shuttle back to the surface. Propose an experiment that would demonstrate beta2-AR membrane proteins are indirectly linked to actin filaments as part of a larger complex. Hypothesis (1 pts): Experimental design/controls (2 pts): Results if correct (1 pts): Results if incorrect (1 pts):", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Paper6", "question_number": "3", "type": "standard", "question": "What is the role of MESNA in this figure?", "choices": ["Cleaves the biotin tag", "Adds the biotin tag", "Labels the protein on the gel", "Stimulates endocytosis"], "correct_answers": ["Cleaves the biotin tag"]}
{"assignment": "Paper6", "question_number": "4", "type": "standard", "question": "Which of the following are independent variables in the control experiment labeled \"uptake wt\"? Mark all that apply", "choices": ["Size of band", "Band intensity", "Time of incubation", "Addition or not of MESNA"], "correct_answers": ["Time of incubation", "Addition or not of MESNA"]}
{"assignment": "Paper6", "question_number": "5", "type": "standard", "question": "Which of the following conclusions about MyoA and MyoB can be made from this figure?", "choices": ["MyoA and MyoB are needed for uptake", "MyoA and MyoB are needed for recycling", "MyoA and MyoB are needed for both processes", "MyoA and MyoB are not needed for either process"], "correct_answers": ["MyoA and MyoB are needed for recycling"]}
{"assignment": "Review1", "question_number": "1-2", "type": "matching", "options": ["Confocal Microscopy", "Standard, Widefield Microscopy"], "matches": [{"prompt": "Top", "answer": "(B)"}, {"prompt": "Bottom", "answer": "(A)"}]}
{"assignment": "Review1", "question_number": "1", "type": "standard", "question": "Top", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Review1", "question_number": "2", "type": "standard", "question": "Bottom", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Review1", "question_number": "3", "type": "standard", "question": "Lipid Experiment: Is your hypothesis correct or incorrect?", "choices": ["Correct", "Incorrect"], "correct_answers": ["Incorrect"]}
{"assignment": "Review1", "question_number": "4", "type": "standard", "question": "Lipid Experiment: Which is more helpful in exploring your hypothesis?", "choices": ["Widefield Microscopy", "Confocal Microscopy"], "correct_answers": ["Confocal Microscopy"]}
{"assignment": "Review1", "question_number": "5", "type": "standard", "question": "You are studying a novel protein that you believe may be a peripheral membrane protein bound to the inner leaflet of the cell membrane. Assuming the tools (antibodies, etc.) are available, which of the following types of microscopy could you use to show that the protein is specifically at the membrane and not throughout the cytoplasm? (mark all that apply) Mark all that apply", "choices": ["Widefield Fluorescence Microscopy", "Confocal Microscopy", "Nomarski Microscopy", "Transmission Electron Microscopy"], "correct_answers": ["Confocal Microscopy", "Transmission Electron Microscopy"]}
{"assignment": "Review1", "question_number": "6", "type": "standard", "question": "Which of the following best defines an antigen?", "choices": ["A molecule that induces an immune response", "The binding site for a particular antibody", "A short sequence of amino-acids that can be added to a gene to create a binding site for an antibody", "None of the above"], "correct_answers": ["A molecule that induces an immune response"]}
{"assignment": "Review1", "question_number": "7", "type": "standard", "question": "Which of the following chromatography techniques will best isolate a single protein?", "choices": ["Ion-exchange chromatography", "Gel filtration chromatography", "Affinity chromatography", "They are all equally able", "None of the above"], "correct_answers": ["Affinity chromatography"]}
{"assignment": "Review1", "question_number": "8", "type": "standard", "question": "If you want to identify genes linked to autism in a mouse model, which genetic approach or approaches could you use? (Mark all that apply) Mark all that apply", "choices": ["Forward Genetics", "Reverse Genetics", "Population Genetics", "Optogenetics"], "correct_answers": ["Forward Genetics"]}
{"assignment": "Review1", "question_number": "9", "type": "standard", "question": "Which of the following are true of forward AND reverse genetic approaches?", "choices": ["A forward genetic screen begins with the DNA sequence and examines the phenotype when the sequence is changed.", "A reverse genetic screen starts with a phenotype and identifies the mutant genes that caused that phenotype.", "Both require an enormous number of mutations to be made to identify a specific phenotype.", "A-C are correct", "None of the above"], "correct_answers": ["None of the above"]}
{"assignment": "Review1", "question_number": "0", "type": "standard", "question": "The lateral diffusion of a plasma membrane protein that binds to proteins on the surface of other cells has been studied using the fluorescence recovery after photobleaching (FRAP) technique on a small area of the cell membrane in a cell under high density growth conditions, and the following plot has been obtained. The cells are then grown under low-density conditions where they do not touch. How would you expect the FRAP curve to change under these new conditions? The dotted line in each graph is the original curve shown for comparison.", "choices": ["Figure A", "Figure B", "Figure C", "Figure D", "Figure E"], "correct_answers": ["Figure B"]}
{"assignment": "Review1", "question_number": "1", "type": "standard", "question": "Which of the following is not a way mentioned in class to modify protein mobility in the membrane?", "choices": ["Attaching to other cells", "Binding scaffolds", "Transport using molecular motors", "Lipid rafts", "Protein complexes that for \"fences\""], "correct_answers": ["Transport using molecular motors"]}
{"assignment": "Review1", "question_number": "2", "type": "standard", "question": "Hydrophobic regions of a protein can indicate either transmembrane domains, or internal core domains (buried in the middle of the protein). What clue on a hydropathy plot can you use to help differentiate between the two?", "choices": ["Transmembrane regions are more hydrophobic than protein cores", "Transmembrane regions are less hydrophobic than protein cores.", "The length of a transmembrane region is limited to 20-25 amino acids; internal core regions can be any length.", "The length of a transmembrane region must be greater than 50 amino acids to allow for alpha-helix formation; internal core regions can be smaller since they are globular in structure.", "Trick question! Amino acid hydropathy plots are too simple to provide information about more complex structures."], "correct_answers": ["The length of a transmembrane region is limited to 20-25 amino acids; internal core regions can be any length."]}
{"assignment": "Review1", "question_number": "3", "type": "standard", "question": "Martian Membranes: Imagine that a new type of cell was discovered on Mars in an organism growing in benzene, a non-polar liquid. The cell has a lipid bilayer made of phospholipids. a) Given the environment, how might the structure of these lipid bilayers differ from ours? b) What amino acid makeup would a transmembrane domain of a Martian membrane protein likely have?", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Review1", "question_number": "4", "type": "standard", "question": "Martian Membranes: Studying these new types of membranes, you find some fatty acids have longer hydrophobic tails than others. Would these tend to sort into rafts?", "choices": ["Yes, because different tail lengths will still tend to separate.", "Yes, because some phospholipid heads are non-polar", "No, because there is not an energetically unfavorable region where tails of different lengths meet.", "No, because all lipid tails would have to be the same length"], "correct_answers": ["No, because there is not an energetically unfavorable region where tails of different lengths meet."]}
{"assignment": "Review1", "question_number": "15-20", "type": "matching", "options": ["", "", "", "", "No filaments will be seen."], "matches": [{"prompt": "Profilin and Formin added", "answer": "(A)"}, {"prompt": "Arp2/3 added", "answer": "(B)"}, {"prompt": "Arp2/3 and CapZ added", "answer": "(C)"}, {"prompt": "Cofilin added", "answer": "(D)"}, {"prompt": "Tropomodulin and Tropomyosin added", "answer": "(A)"}, {"prompt": "High concentrations of thymosin", "answer": "(E)"}]}
{"assignment": "Review1", "question_number": "5", "type": "standard", "question": "Profilin and Formin added", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Review1", "question_number": "6", "type": "standard", "question": "Arp2/3 added", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Review1", "question_number": "7", "type": "standard", "question": "Arp2/3 and CapZ added", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Review1", "question_number": "8", "type": "standard", "question": "Cofilin added", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Review1", "question_number": "9", "type": "standard", "question": "Tropomodulin and Tropomyosin added", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Review1", "question_number": "0", "type": "standard", "question": "High concentrations of thymosin", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Review1", "question_number": "1", "type": "standard", "question": "Arp2/3 is a key regulator of actin polymerization and structure. Which of the following aspects of polymerization is Arp2/3 involved in?", "choices": ["\u200b\u200b\u200b\u200b\u200b\u200bDecreasing filament stability", "Nucleation", "Cutting filaments", "Addition of profilin-bound g-actin"], "correct_answers": ["Nucleation"]}
{"assignment": "Review1", "question_number": "2", "type": "standard", "question": "Which of the following is true concerning actin? (mark all that apply) Mark all that apply", "choices": ["It spontaneously forms filaments in vivo", "It spontaneously forms filaments in vitro", "It is built from asymmetric dimers", "It is built from ATPases (proteins that bind ATP)", "Its stability and growth rates are highly regulated by the cell"], "correct_answers": ["It spontaneously forms filaments in vitro", "It is built from ATPases (proteins that bind ATP)", "Its stability and growth rates are highly regulated by the cell"]}
{"assignment": "Review1", "question_number": "3", "type": "standard", "question": "You are studying the genetics of congenital heart disease. In one of your studies, you find that the gene Camta1 regulates gene expression in response to calcium levels and is actively transcribed in the developing heart. Design a reverse genetics experiment to determine the mutant phenotype of Camta1 in heart development. Make sure to follow the standard format (Hypothesis, experimental design, controls, prediction if hypothesis is correct or incorrect).", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Review2", "question_number": "1-6", "type": "matching", "options": ["MF", "MF, IF", "MT, IF", "MT, MF", "\u200b\u200b\u200b\u200b\u200b\u200bMT", "\u200b\u200b\u200b\u200b\u200b\u200bMT, MF, IF", "\u200b\u200b\u200b\u200b\u200b\u200b\u200bIF"], "matches": [{"prompt": "Found in cilia and flagella", "answer": "(E)"}, {"prompt": "Subunits can bind and hydrolyze GTP", "answer": "(E)"}, {"prompt": "Subunits can bind and hydrolyze ATP", "answer": "(A)"}, {"prompt": "They are formed from repeating dimers", "answer": "(C)"}, {"prompt": "Can replace subunits after it is formed", "answer": "(F)"}, {"prompt": "Must be nucleated in cells by special protein complexes", "answer": "(D)"}]}
{"assignment": "Review2", "question_number": "1", "type": "standard", "question": "Found in cilia and flagella", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Review2", "question_number": "2", "type": "standard", "question": "Subunits can bind and hydrolyze GTP", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Review2", "question_number": "3", "type": "standard", "question": "Subunits can bind and hydrolyze ATP", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Review2", "question_number": "4", "type": "standard", "question": "They are formed from repeating dimers", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Review2", "question_number": "5", "type": "standard", "question": "Can replace subunits after it is formed", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Review2", "question_number": "6", "type": "standard", "question": "Must be nucleated in cells by special protein complexes", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Review2", "question_number": "7", "type": "standard", "question": "Which of the following is true concerning intermediate filaments? (mark all that apply)Mark all that apply", "choices": ["They can grow from either end", "They can fuse together", "They have strong tensile strength", "\u200b\u200b\u200b\u200b\u200b\u200bThey are made of ATPases", "They are made of GTPases"], "correct_answers": ["They can grow from either end", "They can fuse together", "They have strong tensile strength"]}
{"assignment": "Review2", "question_number": "8", "type": "standard", "question": "Which of the following microtubule structures are found in cilia and flagella?", "choices": ["Double ring structure in a 9 + 2 conformation", "Double ring structure in a 9 + 0 conformation", "Triple ring structure in a 9 + 0 conformation", "None of the above"], "correct_answers": ["Double ring structure in a 9 + 2 conformation"]}
{"assignment": "Review2", "question_number": "9", "type": "standard", "question": "Different classes of intermediate filaments can be found in specific cell types. Which of the following intermediate filament classes can create a meshwork?", "choices": ["Vimentin", "Keratin", "Neurofilament", "Lamin", "Nestin"], "correct_answers": ["Lamin"]}
{"assignment": "Review2", "question_number": "0", "type": "standard", "question": "In order to determine the class of a novel microtubule motor you are testing, you fluorescently label tubulin and add it to a mixture with GTP and unlabeled tubulin to make dimly fluorescing microtubules. You then purify the microtubules and add it to a tube with all fluorescently labeled tubulin and GTPgammaS. GTPgammaS has a sulfate in place of the last phosphate to prevent its hydrolysis by GTPases (and thus prevents disassembly during the experiment). You then attach your motor to the glass slide and add the filaments. Here are your results:A) Describe what the picture shows.B) Based on the data, classify your motor using the three criteria discussed in class.C) What class of motor is your protein likely a member of (Myosin (I, II, V, or VI), Kinesin, or Dynein?", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Review2", "question_number": "1", "type": "standard", "question": "Observation of flagella in mobile algae has shown that tubulin subunits and other flagellar materials move toward the tips of flagella at a rate of 2.5 um/min, but materials moving back toward the base of the flagella move at 4 um/min. How do you explain the difference?", "choices": ["Kinesin is faster than Dynein, because Kinesin is processive while Dynein is not", "Dynein is faster than Kinesin, because Dynein is processive while Kinesin is not", "Dynein is faster than Kinesin, perhaps because its step size is larger", "Dynein uses more ATP per step, thus making it stronger", "I don\u2019t know, but I have a sudden craving for turkey legs"], "correct_answers": ["Dynein is faster than Kinesin, perhaps because its step size is larger"]}
{"assignment": "Review2", "question_number": "2", "type": "standard", "question": "After death, the muscles of the body become very stiff and inextensible, and the corpse is said to go into rigor. Which stage of the myosin ATP cycle would the myosin be in during rigor?", "choices": ["Actin-bound and contracted", "Actin-free and relaxed", "Actin-free and cocked", "Actin-bound and cocked"], "correct_answers": ["Actin-bound and contracted"]}
{"assignment": "Review2", "question_number": "3", "type": "standard", "question": "You immobilize myosin to a glass slide and add fluorescently labeled actin and ATP. You observe the actin moving across the slide. You then wash the slide and add a non-hydrolyzable form of ATP. What should you see now?", "choices": ["The actin filaments will float away", "The actin filaments will be attached, but no longer move", "The actin filaments will move in the opposite direction", "This would not work because the actin filaments would be released during the wash step."], "correct_answers": ["The actin filaments will float away"]}
{"assignment": "Review2", "question_number": "4", "type": "standard", "question": "Which of following steps in myosin motor function is associated with hydrolysis of ATP to ADP?", "choices": ["Attachment", "Release", "Cocking", "Power Stroke"], "correct_answers": ["Cocking"]}
{"assignment": "Review2", "question_number": "15-23", "type": "matching", "options": ["Adherens Junctions", "Adherens Junctions, Focal Adhesions, Desmosomes, and Hemidesmosomes", "Adherens Junctions and Desmosomes", "Adherens Junctions and Focal Adhesions", "All", "Desmosomes", "Desmosomes and Hemidesmosomes", "Focal Adhesions", "Focal Adhesions and Hemidesmosomes", "Gap Junctions", "Gap Junctions and Tight Junctions", "Hemidesmosomes", "None", "Tight Junctions"], "matches": [{"prompt": "Associated with either the actin or IF cytoskeleton", "answer": "(B)"}, {"prompt": "Contain transmembrane molecules", "answer": "(E) All"}, {"prompt": "Bind to the Extracellular matrix", "answer": "(I)"}, {"prompt": "Bind to Microtubules", "answer": "(M) None"}, {"prompt": "Create an impermeable seal", "answer": "(N)"}, {"prompt": "Allow the exchange of metabolites between the cytosol of two adjacent cells.", "answer": "(J)"}, {"prompt": "Include Vinculin as an adapter protein", "answer": "(D)"}, {"prompt": "Contain Integrins that can be activated or inactivated", "answer": "(I)"}, {"prompt": "Bound to Intermediate Filaments", "answer": "(G)"}]}
{"assignment": "Review2", "question_number": "5", "type": "standard", "question": "Associated with either the actin or IF cytoskeleton", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Review2", "question_number": "6", "type": "standard", "question": "Contain transmembrane molecules", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Review2", "question_number": "7", "type": "standard", "question": "Bind to the Extracellular matrix", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Review2", "question_number": "8", "type": "standard", "question": "Bind to Microtubules", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Review2", "question_number": "9", "type": "standard", "question": "Create an impermeable seal", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Review2", "question_number": "0", "type": "standard", "question": "Allow the exchange of metabolites between the cytosol of two adjacent cells.", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Review2", "question_number": "1", "type": "standard", "question": "Include Vinculin as an adapter protein", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Review2", "question_number": "2", "type": "standard", "question": "Contain Integrins that can be activated or inactivated", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Review2", "question_number": "3", "type": "standard", "question": "Bound to Intermediate Filaments", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Review2", "question_number": "4", "type": "standard", "question": "Cells expressing either N-cadherin, high levels of E-cadherin, or low levels of E-cadherin have sorted themselves out on a substratum in a cadherin-dependent manner as shown in the schematic drawing below. Which cells would you expect to correspond to white, gray, and black in the drawing, respectively?", "choices": ["Gray=N-Cadherin, White=high levels of E-Cadherin, Black=low levels of E-Cadherin", "Gray=High levels of E-Cadherin, White=Low levels of E-Cadherin, Black=N-Cadherin", "Gray=High levels of E-Cadherin, White=N-Cadherin, Black=low levels of E-Cadherin", "Gray=N-Cadherin, White=Low levels of E-Cadherin, Black=High levels of E-Cadherin"], "correct_answers": ["Gray=N-Cadherin, White=Low levels of E-Cadherin, Black=High levels of E-Cadherin"]}
{"assignment": "Review2", "question_number": "5", "type": "standard", "question": "Recent research has shown that nuclear structure is intimately related to transcriptional regulation. One example is the Baf containing LINC complex. Baf associates directly with chromatin. Which do you think it associates more with, heterochromatin or euchromatin and why?", "choices": ["It associates with heterochromatin, because heterochromatin is found around the edge of the nucleus.", "It associates with euchromatin, because euchromatin is found around the edge of the nucleus.", "It associates with heterochromatin, because heterochromatin is found in the middle of the nucleus.", "It associates with euchromatin, because euchromatin is found in the middle of the nucleus."], "correct_answers": ["It associates with heterochromatin, because heterochromatin is found around the edge of the nucleus."]}
{"assignment": "Review2", "question_number": "6", "type": "standard", "question": "You are studying the process of rRNA creation and maturation. You hypothesize that cleavage of the rRNA is mediated by a snoRNP that recognizes a specific sequence containing a modified base.You designed an antibody to the snoRNP in question. You expect to see staining in...", "choices": ["The whole nucleus", "Only in the nucleolus", "Only in the nucleoplasm outside of the nucleolus", "Around the edges of the nucleus", "In the cytoplasm"], "correct_answers": ["Only in the nucleolus"]}
{"assignment": "Review2", "question_number": "7", "type": "standard", "question": "You are studying the cleavage of the 45S pre-rRNA. Design an experiment to test whether modification of one or more bases in the endonuclease target sequence is necessary for cleavage.Include the following:Hypothesis (1 pt):Experimental Design and Controls [negative and validation or positive controls at a minimum] (2 pts):Results if correct (1 pt):Results if incorrect (1 pt):", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Review3", "question_number": "1", "type": "standard", "question": "What makes a cell unique is not the DNA it contains, but what proteins it contains. Thus, gene expression must be carefully regulated in each cell.Which of the following is/are true about transcription factors? (Mark all that apply) Mark all that apply", "choices": ["They can recruit polymerase II to a promoter", "They can lead to chemical modifications of histone tails", "They bind DNA", "They can interact with other transcription factors"], "correct_answers": ["They can recruit polymerase II to a promoter", "They can lead to chemical modifications of histone tails", "They bind DNA", "They can interact with other transcription factors"]}
{"assignment": "Review3", "question_number": "2", "type": "standard", "question": "Position effects are caused by the natural tendency of chromatin to spread. Which of the following mechanisms can be used by insulator/barrier sequences to arrest the spread of a particular histone mark? (mark all that apply) Mark all that apply", "choices": ["Physical barrier, such as DNA binding to nuclear pore or envelope", "Proteins that bind tightly to histones and prevent their modification", "Recruiting other Histone-modifying proteins that make different modifications", "Binding Polymerase to the promoter", "Ubiquitinating and degrading all of the HAT or HDAC complexes"], "correct_answers": ["Physical barrier, such as DNA binding to nuclear pore or envelope", "Proteins that bind tightly to histones and prevent their modification", "Recruiting other Histone-modifying proteins that make different modifications"]}
{"assignment": "Review3", "question_number": "3", "type": "standard", "question": "You identify a potential transcription factor binding site in the promoter of a gene you are studying. You create two constructs with your promoter upstream of a reporter gene, one wild type and one with the site mutated. You then transfect cells and measure reporter levels. You also measure RNA PolII binding just 5' of the transcribed region. Here are your results: Wildtype promoter: High levels of reporter, PolII is bound to promoter Mutant promoter: Low levels of reporter, PolII is bound to promoter What do you conclude about the binding site?", "choices": ["It is a binding site for a repressor that prevents PolII release from the promoter", "It is a binding site for an activator that prevents PolII release from the promoter", "It is a binding site for a repressor that promotes PolII release from the promoter", "It is a binding site for an activator that promotes PolII release from the promoter"], "correct_answers": ["It is a binding site for an activator that promotes PolII release from the promoter"]}
{"assignment": "Review3", "question_number": "4", "type": "standard", "question": "You suspect that the transcription factor you are working on leads to the formation of heterochromatin that covers a gene upstream and a gene downstream of its binding site. To test this hypothesis, you create a DNA construct with two reporter genes, one upstream and one downstream of the TF binding site and insert into the genome of cells expressing your transcription factor. Both genes are under the control of a strong promoter. However, both reporters are expressed at very low levels. You then insert an insulator sequence into the DNA sequence between your TF binding site and the downstream reporter. Predict the expression levels of both reporters if your hypothesis is correct and incorrect. (Hint: Drawing this out will help with this question.)", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Review3", "question_number": "5", "type": "standard", "question": "Mutations in the ubiquitin pathway can result in diseases with a range of severity. Rank the following by the expected severity (from most to least) of a mutation in a single gene within that class.", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Review3", "question_number": "6", "type": "standard", "question": "Ubiquitination is the process by which proteins are marked for degradation, and is essential for the health of the cell. Which of the following ways can be used by the cell to control when a particular protein is ubiquitinated (mark all that apply)Mark all that apply", "choices": ["Activation of the ubiquitination signal on the target protein", "Activation of a ubiquitin ligase", "Controlled expression of a particular E3 protein", "Activation of the proteasome"], "correct_answers": ["Activation of the ubiquitination signal on the target protein", "Activation of a ubiquitin ligase", "Controlled expression of a particular E3 protein"]}
{"assignment": "Review3", "question_number": "7", "type": "standard", "question": "Which ubiquitin ligase directly uses ATP?", "choices": ["E1", "E2", "E3", "E4"], "correct_answers": ["E1"]}
{"assignment": "Review3", "question_number": "8", "type": "standard", "question": "How can the cell increase the amount of protein present? Mark all that apply", "choices": ["Increase the rate of translation", "Decrease the rate of translation", "Increase the rate of degradation", "Decrease the rate of degradation"], "correct_answers": ["Increase the rate of translation", "Decrease the rate of degradation"]}
{"assignment": "Review3", "question_number": "9", "type": "standard", "question": "The nuclear pore and importin work together to control which proteins move into the nucleus. The HIV virus has a number of proteins that hijack the normal cellular machinery to enter the nucleus and aid viral replication. In order to determine which importin was essential for a particular HIV protein (REV), researchers permeabilized cells, which allows free floating proteins to be removed, but leaves membrane structures and associated proteins. They then add RAN-GTP, a YFP-REV fusion and a single importin (listed above each panel). Which importin transports HIV REV into the nucleus.", "choices": ["imp beta", "imp 5", "imp7", "imp 9", "imp 13"], "correct_answers": ["imp 9"]}
{"assignment": "Review3", "question_number": "10-15", "type": "matching", "options": ["The rate would not change initially", "The rate would initially increase", "The rate would initially decrease"], "matches": [{"prompt": "A mutation in the channel nucleoporins that removes their tails", "answer": "(B)"}, {"prompt": "The importin for your NLS (loss of function)", "answer": "(C)"}, {"prompt": "An exportin (loss of function)", "answer": "(A)"}, {"prompt": "A mutation that removes the cytoplasmic tails of the scaffold nucleoporins", "answer": "(C)"}, {"prompt": "Ran GEF (loss of function)", "answer": "(C)"}, {"prompt": "Ran GAP (loss of function)", "answer": "(C)"}]}
{"assignment": "Review3", "question_number": "0", "type": "standard", "question": "A mutation in the channel nucleoporins that removes their tails", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Review3", "question_number": "1", "type": "standard", "question": "The importin for your NLS (loss of function)", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Review3", "question_number": "2", "type": "standard", "question": "An exportin (loss of function)", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Review3", "question_number": "3", "type": "standard", "question": "A mutation that removes the cytoplasmic tails of the scaffold nucleoporins", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Review3", "question_number": "4", "type": "standard", "question": "Ran GEF (loss of function)", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Review3", "question_number": "5", "type": "standard", "question": "Ran GAP (loss of function)", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Review3", "question_number": "6", "type": "standard", "question": "Ran proteins are part of a large family of GTPases. These GTPases are found playing many roles in the cell, and constitute one of the common patterns we will see throughout the semester. Therefore, understanding their role is essential. Which of the following is true about small GTPases...", "choices": ["Their GTP is hydrolyzed to GDP by a GAP", "They hydrolyze their bound GTP when activated by a GAP", "They hydrolyze their bound GTP when activated by a GEF", "The GEF hydrolyzes GDP", "None of the above"], "correct_answers": ["They hydrolyze their bound GTP when activated by a GAP"]}
{"assignment": "Review3", "question_number": "7", "type": "standard", "question": "You conduct a co-immunoprecipitation with a pull-down using an anti-ran antibody and a blot with an anti-importin antibody. Describe the resulting western blot for the experiments in the presence of GTP and GDP, respectively.", "choices": ["The western blot would show a band in the bead fraction in the presence of GTP and in the supernatant fraction in the presence of GDP", "The western blot would show a band in the bead fraction in the presence of GDP and in the supernatant fraction in the presence of GTP", "The western blot would show a band in the bead fraction for both GTP and GDP", "The western blot would show a band in the supernatant fraction for both GTP and GDP"], "correct_answers": ["The western blot would show a band in the bead fraction in the presence of GTP and in the supernatant fraction in the presence of GDP"]}
{"assignment": "Review3", "question_number": "8", "type": "standard", "question": "Which of the following is true of mitochondrial inheritance? (mark all that apply)Mark all that apply", "choices": ["Mitochondrial alleles are mainly inherited through the maternal line", "All cells contain the same mitochondrial disease", "Diseases arising from mutations in the mitochondrial genome can become more severe in subsequent generations", "Mutations in mitochondrial genes have little effect because there are copies of the genes in the nuclear genome"], "correct_answers": ["Mitochondrial alleles are mainly inherited through the maternal line", "Diseases arising from mutations in the mitochondrial genome can become more severe in subsequent generations"]}
{"assignment": "Review3", "question_number": "9", "type": "standard", "question": "ATP synthase is directly driven by...", "choices": ["Electrons provided by FADH and NADH", "Electrons from the electron transport chain", "Protons moving down an electrochemical concentration gradient", "All of the above"], "correct_answers": ["Protons moving down an electrochemical concentration gradient"]}
{"assignment": "Review3", "question_number": "0", "type": "standard", "question": "Your friend is dating a guy who admits that he has a mild form of mitochondrial disease (mitochondrial disease has a wide range of severity). She is now worried that there is a chance if they continue their relationship, their future children will get the disease. You look on Wikipedia and find that mitochondrial disease can be caused by nuclear and mitochondrial mutations, depending on the case. You ask your friend to give you a pedigree with everyone with the disease marked (in pink). She gives it to you and and tells you her boyfriend is the only male in the youngest generation with the disease. What do you advise your friend? Justify your answer.", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Review4", "question_number": "1", "type": "standard", "question": "You are studying the roles of the SRP, so you purify microsomes and mix them with the materials necessary for translation (ribosomes, tRNAs, etc.) and an mRNA coding for an ER signal sequence fused to the GFP coding region. You then incubate the mixture with one of several SRP variants (see below), spin in a centrifuge, and then run the microsome and supernatant fractions on an SDS-PAGE gel and do a western blot with an antibody against GFP. The following conditions represent the lanes you would have on the two gels (microsome and supernatant fractions) you are running. Indicate in each condition whether you will see a band in the microsome fraction gel, the supernatant fraction gel, both or neither. Also indicate whether each is control or experimental. i. No SRP added to the mixture ii. WT SRP iii. SRP with the SRP receptor binding domain mutated iv. SRP with the translation-blocking domain mutated v. SRP with the signal peptide binding domain mutated", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Review4", "question_number": "2", "type": "standard", "question": "Which of the following is/are characteristic of signal peptides? (mark all that apply)Mark all that apply", "choices": ["They have an exact sequence of Amino Acids", "They are always cleaved", "They contain mainly hydrophobic amino acids", "They are most often, but not always, located at the N terminus of the protein"], "correct_answers": ["They contain mainly hydrophobic amino acids", "They are most often, but not always, located at the N terminus of the protein"]}
{"assignment": "Review4", "question_number": "3", "type": "standard", "question": "Which of the following is true regarding the ribosomes involved in co-translational translocation? ( mark all that apply)Mark all that apply", "choices": ["They contain a unique set of components to allow translation at the ER membrane", "They can form polysomes on a single mRNA", "They start translation in the cytosol", "They are anchored to the ER membrane during co-translational translocation by the peptide they are making"], "correct_answers": ["They can form polysomes on a single mRNA", "They start translation in the cytosol", "They are anchored to the ER membrane during co-translational translocation by the peptide they are making"]}
{"assignment": "Review4", "question_number": "4", "type": "standard", "question": "You are experimenting on the control of vesicle budding by Sar1. As part of your experiments, you mix microsomes, Sar1, coat assembly proteins and either GTP\u03b3S (non-hydrolyzable form of GTP), GDP\u03b2S (cannot be exchanged) or normal GTP. Assume that Sar1 is the limiting component of your experiment. Which guanine variant would result in the most vesicles?", "choices": ["GTP\u03b3S (non-hydrolyzable form of GTP)", "GDP\u03b2S (cannot be exchanged)", "normal GTP", "normal GDP"], "correct_answers": ["normal GTP"]}
{"assignment": "Review4", "question_number": "5-8", "type": "matching", "options": ["No vesicles", "Both kinds", "Coated vesicles only", "Uncoated vesicles only"], "matches": [{"prompt": "GTP\u03b3S", "answer": "(C)"}, {"prompt": "GDP\u03b2S", "answer": "(A) No vesicles"}, {"prompt": "GTP", "answer": "(B) Both kinds"}, {"prompt": "GDP", "answer": "(A) No vesicles"}]}
{"assignment": "Review4", "question_number": "5", "type": "standard", "question": "GTP\u03b3S", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Review4", "question_number": "6", "type": "standard", "question": "GDP\u03b2S", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Review4", "question_number": "7", "type": "standard", "question": "GTP", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Review4", "question_number": "8", "type": "standard", "question": "GDP", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Review4", "question_number": "9", "type": "standard", "question": "Vesicle Transport Specific cargos are concentrated into ER vesicles destined for the Golgi. This is accomplished by transmembrane proteins that bind cargo on the luminal side and . . .", "choices": ["activate Arf1 on the cytoplasmic side", "bend the ER membrane to create a vesicle", "are recruited to budding vesicles by binding Arf1-GTP", "are recruited to budding vesicles by binding Arf1-GDP", "are recruited to budding vesicles by binding scaffold proteins"], "correct_answers": ["are recruited to budding vesicles by binding scaffold proteins"]}
{"assignment": "Review4", "question_number": "10-21", "type": "matching", "options": ["recycled by vesicles", "released into cytoplasm", "no need to recycle"], "matches": [{"prompt": "Cargo receptors in the ER", "answer": "(A)"}, {"prompt": "Sar1", "answer": "(B)"}, {"prompt": "Rabs on vesicles", "answer": "(B)"}, {"prompt": "Rabs on target membrane", "answer": "(C)"}, {"prompt": "Rab GEFs", "answer": "(C)"}, {"prompt": "Rab GAPs", "answer": "(C)"}, {"prompt": "CopII", "answer": "(B)"}, {"prompt": "CopI", "answer": "(B)"}, {"prompt": "V-snares", "answer": "(A)"}, {"prompt": "T-snare", "answer": "(C)"}, {"prompt": "Scaffold proteins", "answer": "(B)"}, {"prompt": "Snap25", "answer": "(C)"}]}
{"assignment": "Review4", "question_number": "0", "type": "standard", "question": "Cargo receptors in the ER", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Review4", "question_number": "1", "type": "standard", "question": "Sar1", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Review4", "question_number": "2", "type": "standard", "question": "Rabs on vesicles", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Review4", "question_number": "3", "type": "standard", "question": "Rabs on target membrane", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Review4", "question_number": "4", "type": "standard", "question": "Rab GEFs", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Review4", "question_number": "5", "type": "standard", "question": "Rab GAPs", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Review4", "question_number": "6", "type": "standard", "question": "CopII", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Review4", "question_number": "7", "type": "standard", "question": "CopI", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Review4", "question_number": "8", "type": "standard", "question": "V-snares", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Review4", "question_number": "9", "type": "standard", "question": "T-snare", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Review4", "question_number": "0", "type": "standard", "question": "Scaffold proteins", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Review4", "question_number": "1", "type": "standard", "question": "Snap25", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Review4", "question_number": "2", "type": "standard", "question": "You have identified a novel Rab protein. Using fluorescent confocal microscopy, you have determined that it localizes to the Golgi network. However, it is unclear by microscopy whether it is a vesicle-associated Rab or a target membrane-associated Rab.Describe how to conduct a genetic experiment using the normal format for this class (Hypothesis, design, controls, predicted results). In your predicted results, include whether the rab is vesicle-bound and whether it is Golgi-bound.", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Review4", "question_number": "3", "type": "standard", "question": "In the experiment, you are adding both ATP and GTP. If both the vesicles and the target membrane already have Rab proteins associated, which of these is necessary to have in the solution?", "choices": ["ATP only", "GTP only", "Both", "Neither"], "correct_answers": ["ATP only"]}
{"assignment": "Review4", "question_number": "4", "type": "standard", "question": "Predict whether you will see vesicle fusion during the first and fifth rounds in both your control and experimental groups. Justify your answer.", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Review4", "question_number": "5", "type": "standard", "question": "During Golgi transport, cargo proteins are moved from the cis face to the trans face of the Golgi by cisternal maturation. According to this model, how are resident glycosylases maintained in the correct cisterna?", "choices": ["They remain in the same cisterna while cargo proteins move by anterograde vesicular transport.", "They remain in the same cisterna while cargo proteins move by retrograde vesicular transport.", "They are transported to the next cisterna via retrograde vesicular transport while cargo proteins remain in the same cisterna as it moves through the Golgi.", "They are transported to the next cisterna via anterograde vesicular transport while cargo proteins remain in the same cisterna as it moves through the Golgi."], "correct_answers": ["They are transported to the next cisterna via retrograde vesicular transport while cargo proteins remain in the same cisterna as it moves through the Golgi."]}
{"assignment": "Review4", "question_number": "6", "type": "standard", "question": "Cystic fibrosis is a deadly disease that is caused by mutations in an ion channel (the CFTR gene) located on the cell membrane. Patients exhibit symptoms due to a lack of the protein on the cell surface, even though the mutant protein is functional in vitro. You hypothesize that the mutations cause the protein to be caught in the misfolded protein response. As this response depends on glycosylation, you identify glycosylation sites and find two locations\u2014N894 and N900. To test the effect of glycosylation at these sites on protein degradation, you label and tracked the amount of protein over time using WT or mutant forms of CFTR that block glycosylation. The results of this experiment are shown below:From this data, what can you conclude about the role of glycosylation on CFTR? (hint: make sure to compare each timepoint to the zero timepoint in each gel.)", "choices": ["N894 glycosylation increases stability", "N900 glycosylation increases stability", "Both increase stability", "Neither increases stability"], "correct_answers": ["N900 glycosylation increases stability"]}
{"assignment": "Review4", "question_number": "7", "type": "standard", "question": "Movement of proteins through the Golgi allows their stepwise modification. In the cisternal maturation model, this is accomplished by . . . (mark all that apply) Mark all that apply", "choices": ["Using vesicle transport to move the proteins being modified between cisternae", "Altering the glycosylase composition of the cisterna as it moves through the Golgi", "Using vesicle transport to move resident glycosylases between cisternae", "Creating new cisternae by fusing vesicles on the Cis side of the Golgi"], "correct_answers": ["Altering the glycosylase composition of the cisterna as it moves through the Golgi", "Using vesicle transport to move resident glycosylases between cisternae", "Creating new cisternae by fusing vesicles on the Cis side of the Golgi"]}
{"assignment": "Review5", "question_number": "1", "type": "standard", "question": "During Golgi transport, cargo proteins are moved from the cis face to the trans face of the Golgi by cisternal maturation. According to this model, how are resident glycosylases maintained in the correct cisterna?", "choices": ["They remain in the same cisterna while cargo proteins move by anterograde vesicular transport.", "They remain in the same cisterna while cargo proteins move by retrograde vesicular transport.", "They are transported to the next cisterna via retrograde vesicular transport while cargo proteins remain in the same cisterna as it moves through the Golgi.", "They are transported to the next cisterna via anterograde vesicular transport while cargo proteins remain in the same cisterna as it moves through the Golgi."], "correct_answers": ["They are transported to the next cisterna via retrograde vesicular transport while cargo proteins remain in the same cisterna as it moves through the Golgi."]}
{"assignment": "Review5", "question_number": "2", "type": "standard", "question": "Cystic fibrosis is a deadly disease that is caused by mutations in an ion channel (the CFTR gene) located on the cell membrane. Patients exhibit symptoms due to a lack of the protein on the cell surface, even though the mutant protein is functional in vitro. You hypothesize that the mutations cause the protein to be caught in the misfolded protein response. As this response depends on glycosylation, you identify glycosylation sites and find two locations\u2014N894 and N900. To test the effect of glycosylation at these sites on protein degradation, you label and tracked the amount of protein over time using WT or mutant forms of CFTR that block glycosylation. The results of this experiment are shown below:From this data, what can you conclude about the role of glycosylation on CFTR? (hint: make sure to compare each timepoint to the zero timepoint in each gel.)", "choices": ["N894 glycosylation increases stability", "N900 glycosylation increases stability", "Both increase stability", "Neither increases stability"], "correct_answers": ["N900 glycosylation increases stability"]}
{"assignment": "Review5", "question_number": "3", "type": "standard", "question": "How many transmembrane domains are there?", "choices": ["1", "2", "4", "7"], "correct_answers": ["7"]}
{"assignment": "Review5", "question_number": "4", "type": "standard", "question": "Which amino acids will be cleaved by signal peptidase, and which of these are hydrophobic?", "choices": ["1-25 will be cleaved, 10-18 are hydrophobic", "1-25 are all hydrophobic and cleaved", "10-18 are all hydrophobic and will be cleaved", "1-18 will be cleaved, 10-18 are hydrophobic"], "correct_answers": ["1-25 will be cleaved, 10-18 are hydrophobic"]}
{"assignment": "Review5", "question_number": "5", "type": "standard", "question": "Which of the following are glycosylation sites? Mark all that apply", "choices": ["Amino Acid 1", "Amino Acid 26", "Amino Acid 46", "Amino Acid 74"], "correct_answers": ["Amino Acid 46", "Amino Acid 74"]}
{"assignment": "Review5", "question_number": "6", "type": "standard", "question": "Clatherin coated vesicle are essential for initiating endocytosis. \u200b\u200b\u200b\u200b\u200b\u200bPI3K is a kinase that acts on the 3rd carbon in PI(4,5)P2. PTEN is a phosphatase that acts on the same carbon. Which of the following best describes the effect of these proteins on endocytosis?", "choices": ["\u200b\u200b\u200b\u200b\u200b\u200bPI3K activates endocytosis, PTEN represses it.", "\u200b\u200b\u200b\u200b\u200b\u200bPTEN activates endocytosis, PI3K represses it.", "\u200b\u200b\u200b\u200b\u200b\u200bPTEN activates endocytosis, PI3K has no effect.", "\u200b\u200b\u200b\u200b\u200b\u200bPI3K activates endocytosis, PTEN has no effect."], "correct_answers": ["\u200b\u200b\u200b\u200b\u200b\u200bPTEN activates endocytosis, PI3K represses it."]}
{"assignment": "Review5", "question_number": "7", "type": "standard", "question": "Feedback loops can provide important temporal control of signaling pathways. There are many different MAPK type pathways. Below is the signaling activity of a MAPK pathway, NGF, with ligand added at 0 minutes and removed after 15 minutes. What can you conclude from this pattern?", "choices": ["The NGF pathway includes a positive feedback loop", "The NGF pathway includes a negative feedback loop", "The NGF pathway does not have any feedback"], "correct_answers": ["The NGF pathway includes a positive feedback loop"]}
{"assignment": "Review5", "question_number": "8", "type": "standard", "question": "How does the expression of Delta on the surface of a cell activate the expression of certain genes in the nucleus of its neighbor?", "choices": ["Delta binding activates Notch, which activates a transcriptional activator through the JAK-STAT pathway.", "Delta binding leads to stabilization of a cytoskeleton-associated transcriptional activator.", "\u200b\u200b\u200b\u200b\u200b\u200bDelta binding releases the intracellular tail of Notch, which enters the nucleus and promotes transcription of target genes.", "\u200b\u200b\u200b\u200b\u200b\u200bDelta leads to Notch-mediated recruitment of protein complexes to the plasma membrane, resulting in degradation of a transcriptional repressor.", "Delta binds Notch and trigger signaling through a kinase cascade."], "correct_answers": ["\u200b\u200b\u200b\u200b\u200b\u200bDelta binding releases the intracellular tail of Notch, which enters the nucleus and promotes transcription of target genes."]}
{"assignment": "Review5", "question_number": "9", "type": "standard", "question": "The characteristics of a pathway (length, presence of feedback loops, etc.) will determine its response.You fuse GFP to a gene that is up-regulated in response to a signaling pathway you are studying. You then stimulate cells with the ligand for your pathway and view the cells under a fluorescent microscope. What does the following picture tell you about your pathway? (mark all that apply) Mark all that apply", "choices": ["The pathway produces a binary response", "The pathway produces a linear response", "The pathway likely has many amplification steps (e.g. RTK)", "The dose given is sufficient to activate all cells"], "correct_answers": ["The pathway produces a binary response", "The pathway likely has many amplification steps (e.g. RTK)"]}
{"assignment": "Review5", "question_number": "0", "type": "standard", "question": "\u200b\u200b\u200b\u200b\u200b\u200bYou conduct an experiment where you mutate the kinase domain of an RTK receptor and express it in cells (wild-type is still made). You then add ligand and radioactive phosphate to the cell culture and measure phosphorylation of the WT and mutated receptors. Will you see phosphorylation? If so, on which version of the receptor? Justify your answer.", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Review5", "question_number": "1", "type": "standard", "question": "Many cancerous cells (marked by cells repeatedly dividing when they shouldn't) have either loss-of-function mutations, where the protein is no longer functional, or gain-of-function mutations, where the protein is permanently activated, in proteins involved in signaling feedback loops. You are studying a signaling pathway that stimulates cell division and has the topology shown below. You have found a mutation in protein B that induces cancer in cultured fibroblasts. Is this more likely a gain-of-function or loss-of-function? Justify your answer.", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Review5", "question_number": "2", "type": "standard", "question": "You believe that two signaling molecules bind only in the presence of a hormone. To test this hypothesis, your professor asks you to conduct a FRET experiment. You make genes containing BFP or GFP attached to each of your proteins and insert them into the genome of a cell line. BFP can be excited at 440 nm, and emits maximally at 470 nm. GFP is excited at 470 nm and emits maximally at 500 nm. What would be your expected results if your hypothesis is correct?", "choices": ["Emission at 470 nm and 500 nm will be high in the presence of the hormone.", "Emission at 470 nm will be high without hormone and emission at 500 nm will be high with the hormone", "Emission will only be high at 500 nm.", "Emission at 500 nm will be high without hormone and emission at 470 nm will be high with the hormone"], "correct_answers": ["Emission at 470 nm will be high without hormone and emission at 500 nm will be high with the hormone"]}
{"assignment": "Review5", "question_number": "3", "type": "standard", "question": "You are analyzing a novel pathway you think may be involved in cancer. You have identified two members (we will call them A and B) of the pathway and want to determine their relative order. Bioinformatic analysis has predicted that they are likely kinases. You make two FRET probes similar to the hinge design presented in class by inserting the putative phosphorylation sites of protein A or protein B into each probe. You then measure fluorescence of each in cells with either A or B mutated. Your results are in the table below. What can you conclude?", "choices": ["A comes immediately before B", "B comes immediately before A", "A is earlier in the pathway than B, but you do not know if it is immediately before", "B is earlier in the pathway than A, but you do not know if it is immediately before", "Cannot be determined from these results"], "correct_answers": ["B is earlier in the pathway than A, but you do not know if it is immediately before"]}
{"assignment": "Review5", "question_number": "4", "type": "standard", "question": "You are analyzing a protein that you believe affects endocytosis, but you are not sure which stage. You create cells with your gene of interest mutated in the genome, and a tet-off system driving a wild-type (WT) copy of your gene (tet-off allows a specific gene to be turned off by adding a tetracycline family drug). Which of the following best describes expression of your gene in these cells? (mark all that apply)Mark all that apply", "choices": ["The WT version of the gene is expressed when tetracycline is present only", "\u200b\u200b\u200b\u200b\u200b\u200bThe WT version of the gene is expressed when tetracycline is absent only", "\u200b\u200b\u200b\u200b\u200b\u200bThe WT version of the gene is never expressed", "\u200b\u200b\u200b\u200b\u200b\u200bThe mutant copy is always expressed, but likely not functional", "\u200b\u200b\u200b\u200b\u200b\u200bThe mutant copy is never expressed"], "correct_answers": ["\u200b\u200b\u200b\u200b\u200b\u200bThe WT version of the gene is expressed when tetracycline is absent only", "\u200b\u200b\u200b\u200b\u200b\u200bThe mutant copy is always expressed, but likely not functional"]}
{"assignment": "Review5", "question_number": "5", "type": "standard", "question": "Virus Entry. Australian bat lyssaviras (ABLV), a virus closely related to rabies virus, causes neuro-degeneration in humans. It has a glycoprotein on its surface that attaches to and stimulates a receptor on the cell surface. Researchers wanted to know if the drug dynosore (that is a real drug name, don\u2019t blame me) could be used to treat the disease. They flooded cells with virus in the presence or absence of the drug. They then waited varying amounts of time and measured the amount of virus taken up into the cells (y-axis). In the treated cells, they also washed out the media (all drug and unbound virus are removed) at 25 minutes and waited additional amounts of time before measuring virus uptake. Which of the following interpretations is consistent with their results?", "choices": ["Dynosore has no effect on virus uptake, because the washout looks like the control.", "Dynosore has no effect on virus uptake, because the hollow circle line is flat.", "Dynosore prevents uptake, but not surface binding of the virus, because the hollow circle line is flat and then virus uptake increases after washout.", "\u200b\u200b\u200b\u200b\u200b\u200bDynosore prevents surface binding of the virus as long as it is present."], "correct_answers": ["Dynosore prevents uptake, but not surface binding of the virus, because the hollow circle line is flat and then virus uptake increases after washout."]}
{"assignment": "Review5", "question_number": "6", "type": "standard", "question": "As its name suggests, Dynosore inhibits Dynamin. What stage of endocytosis would this most directly inhibit?", "choices": ["Vesicle Formation", "Recycling", "MVB Formation", "Endosome Maturation", "Lysosome Fusion"], "correct_answers": ["Vesicle Formation"]}
{"assignment": "Review5", "question_number": "7", "type": "standard", "question": "Which of the cellular processes listed below would also be affected by inhibiting dynamin? Mark all that apply", "choices": ["Nuclear Transport", "Mitochondrial Fission", "Phagocytosis", "Pinocytosis", "ER to Golgi Transport"], "correct_answers": ["Mitochondrial Fission", "Pinocytosis"]}
{"assignment": "Review5", "question_number": "8", "type": "standard", "question": "Which phosphoinositols are involved in receptor-mediated endocytosis and phagocytosis, and what is their role in each? Based on this information, can you have receptor-mediated endocytosis and phagocytosis at the same time?", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Review5", "question_number": "9", "type": "standard", "question": "Which of the following characteristics is shared between all three endocytic pathways?", "choices": ["They are all activated by receptors", "They all occur all the time", "They all end with fusion to the lysosome", "They all form multivesicular bodies", "They all use GTPases"], "correct_answers": ["They all end with fusion to the lysosome"]}
{"assignment": "Review6", "question_number": "1-6", "type": "matching", "options": ["Adhesion", "Adhesion/Translocation", "De-adhesion", "Extension", "Extension/Adhesion", "Extension/De-adhesion", "Extension/Translocation", "Translocation (contraction)", "Translocation/De-adhesion"], "matches": [{"prompt": "A toxin, C3 transferase, from the bacteria Clostridium botulinum that covalently attaches to Rho, blocking function.", "answer": "(H)"}, {"prompt": "Bathing the cells in GDP-beta-S.", "answer": "(G)"}, {"prompt": "Creating a phosphomimetic mutation in FAK.", "answer": "(C) De-adhesion"}, {"prompt": "A mutation in an arp2/3 subunit.", "answer": "(D) Extension"}, {"prompt": "A mutation in the myosin II expressed in the cell you are studying.", "answer": "(H)"}, {"prompt": "A null mutation affecting Rac1.", "answer": "(D) Extension"}]}
{"assignment": "Review6", "question_number": "1", "type": "standard", "question": "A toxin, C3 transferase, from the bacteria Clostridium botulinum that covalently attaches to Rho, blocking function.", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Review6", "question_number": "2", "type": "standard", "question": "Bathing the cells in GDP-beta-S.", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Review6", "question_number": "3", "type": "standard", "question": "Creating a phosphomimetic mutation in FAK.", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Review6", "question_number": "4", "type": "standard", "question": "A mutation in an arp2/3 subunit.", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Review6", "question_number": "5", "type": "standard", "question": "A mutation in the myosin II expressed in the cell you are studying.", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Review6", "question_number": "6", "type": "standard", "question": "A null mutation affecting Rac1.", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Review6", "question_number": "7", "type": "standard", "question": "The following data shows the concentration of a particular protein in a cell after addition of a chemoattractant (see image). Which of the following protein(s) could this be? (mark all that apply) Mark all that apply", "choices": ["Chemoattractant receptors", "PI3K", "Rac1", "PTEN", "FAK"], "correct_answers": ["PI3K", "Rac1"]}
{"assignment": "Review6", "question_number": "8", "type": "standard", "question": "Cells are treated with a chemical that knocks down expression of PTEN to undetectable levels. When these cells are put into a chemotactic gradient where they will normally start directed cell migration, you now expect to see the cells . . .", "choices": ["Migrate into the gradient", "Migrate out of the gradient", "Migrate in random directions if at all"], "correct_answers": ["Migrate in random directions if at all"]}
{"assignment": "Review6", "question_number": "9", "type": "standard", "question": "You place some cells into a chemoattractant gradient and they begin migrating towards the source of the chemoattractant. You then stain the cells for the chemoattractant receptor and find it localized at\u2026", "choices": ["The front of the moving cell, exclusively", "The rear of the moving cell, exclusively", "Enriched at the front of the moving cell", "Enriched at the rear of the moving cell", "Evenly distributed in the cell membrane"], "correct_answers": ["Evenly distributed in the cell membrane"]}
{"assignment": "Review6", "question_number": "0", "type": "standard", "question": "You are studying planar cell polarity in the developing chick epidermis. You hypothesize that all feathers go in the same direction because of planar cell polarity established near the head of the embryo. To test this, you take cells expressing exclusively Frizzled and Disheveled in the head region of a chick embryo and transplant them to the middle region of the same embryo. If your hypothesis is correct, which way will the feathers point in the embryo?", "choices": ["They will still point from head to tail", "They will all point toward the head", "They will point outward from the new organizer position", "They will be randomly oriented"], "correct_answers": ["They will point outward from the new organizer position"]}
{"assignment": "Review6", "question_number": "9", "type": "standard", "question": "Which of the following accurately describes the Anaphase Promoting Complex? (Mark all that apply)Mark all that apply", "choices": ["It is an E3 Ubiquitin Ligase", "It is a Cyclin", "It causes the degradation of separase", "It causes the degradation of securin"], "correct_answers": ["It is an E3 Ubiquitin Ligase", "It causes the degradation of securin"]}
{"assignment": "Review6", "question_number": "0", "type": "standard", "question": "Which of the following cell cycle transitions does not include a checkpoint?", "choices": ["G1/S", "S/G2", "G2/M", "Metaphase-Anaphase"], "correct_answers": ["S/G2"]}
{"assignment": "Review6", "question_number": "1", "type": "standard", "question": "During the DNA damage checkpoint, which protein binds to Cyclin-CDK complexes to block their function?", "choices": ["ATM/ATR", "P53", "P27", "AuroraB"], "correct_answers": ["P27"]}
{"assignment": "Review6", "question_number": "22-29", "type": "matching", "options": ["Both", "Extrinsic Apoptosis", "Intrinsic Apoptosis"], "matches": [{"prompt": "FADD", "answer": "(B)"}, {"prompt": "Apoptosome", "answer": "(C)"}, {"prompt": "Apaf1", "answer": "(C)"}, {"prompt": "Bcl-2", "answer": "(C)"}, {"prompt": "Bax, Bad", "answer": "(C)"}, {"prompt": "Cytochrome C", "answer": "(C)"}, {"prompt": "iCAD", "answer": "(A) Both"}, {"prompt": "Flipase", "answer": "(A) Both"}]}
{"assignment": "Review6", "question_number": "2", "type": "standard", "question": "FADD", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Review6", "question_number": "3", "type": "standard", "question": "Apoptosome", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Review6", "question_number": "4", "type": "standard", "question": "Apaf1", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Review6", "question_number": "5", "type": "standard", "question": "Bcl-2", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Review6", "question_number": "6", "type": "standard", "question": "Bax, Bad", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Review6", "question_number": "7", "type": "standard", "question": "Cytochrome C", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Review6", "question_number": "8", "type": "standard", "question": "iCAD", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Review6", "question_number": "9", "type": "standard", "question": "Flipase", "choices": [], "correct_answers": []}
{"assignment": "Review6", "question_number": "0", "type": "standard", "question": "In many autoimmune diseases, normal proteins are displayed on the surface in a way that makes them look foreign. This induces apoptosis, most likely through the...", "choices": ["Extrinsic Pathway", "Intrinsic Pathway", "Neither Pathway", "It is impossible to know with the information given"], "correct_answers": ["Extrinsic Pathway"]}
{"assignment": "Review6", "question_number": "1", "type": "standard", "question": "During apoptosis, flipase exchanges the lipids on the inside and outside of the plasma membrane. This aids\u2026", "choices": ["Phagocytosis of the dead cell", "Nuclear envelope breakdown", "DNA cleavage", "Caspase activation", "All of the above"], "correct_answers": ["Phagocytosis of the dead cell"]}
{"assignment": "Review6", "question_number": "2", "type": "standard", "question": "Apoptosis is initiated by conversion of inactive procaspases to active, proteolytic caspases (the initiator caspases). These caspases enact the apoptotic program by . . .", "choices": ["Cleaving other caspases and activating them", "Cleaving and activating other (non-caspase) proteins", "Cleaving and inactivating iCAD", "All of the above"], "correct_answers": ["Cleaving other caspases and activating them"]}
